export const upgradeMapData = {
    aiCenter: {
        level01: {
            keyPoints:[
                "Artificial intelligence refers to the ability of a machine to learn patterns and make predictions. AI does not replace human decisions; instead, AI adds value to human judgment.",
                "AI performs tasks without human intervention and completes mundane and repetitive tasks, while augmented intelligence allows humans to make final decisions after analyzing data, reports, and other types of data.",
                "The three levels of AI include: Narrow AI, Broad AI, and General AI. Narrow AI and Broad AI are available today. In fact, most enterprises use Broad AI. General AI won’t come online until sometime in the future.",
                "The history of AI has progressed across the Era of Tabulation, Era of Programming, and Era of AI.",
                "Data can be structured, unstructured, or semi-structured. <li>Structured data is quantitative and highly organized, such as a spreadsheet of data. <li>Unstructured data is qualitative and lacks structure, such as medical records. It's becoming increasingly valuable to businesses. <li>Semi-structured data combines features of both structured and unstructured data, using metadata.",
                "About 80% of all the data in today’s world is unstructured.",
                "Machine learning has advantages compared to programmable computers. Machine learning can predict and machine learning learns!",
                "Machine learning uses three methods.<li>Supervised learning requires enough examples to make accurate predictions. <li>Unsupervised learning requires large amounts of information so the machine can ask a question, and then figure out how to answer the question by itself. <li>Reinforcement learning requires the process of trial and error.",
                "With AI everywhere, AI will move into all industries, from finance, to education, to healthcare.",
                "AI can increase productivity, create new opportunities, provide deeper insights, and enable personalization.AI can increase productivity, create new opportunities, provide deeper insights, and enable personalization."
            ],
            quizes: {
                quiz01: {
                    question: "Which of the following is a key attribute of an artificial intelligence system?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "AI systems can judge.",
                        option02: "AI systems make predictions.",
                        option03: "AI systems have experience.",
                        option04: "AI systems are self-aware."
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "AI systems make predictions based on data analysis and calculations."
                },
                quiz02: {
                    question: "In which of the following eras of computing did an IBM system beat a chess champion, a robot drive itself down a 131-mile desert trail, and IBM Watson beat two Jeopardy! grand champions?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Era of Programming",
                        option02: "Era of AI",
                        option03: "Era of Tabulation",
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "All of those events occurred in the Era of AI. In 1997, IBM’s Deep Blue beat the world’s chess champion by processing over 200 million possible moves per second. In 2005, a Stanford University robot drove itself down a 131-mile desert trail. And in 2011, IBM’s Watson defeated two grand champions in the game of Jeopardy!"
                },
                quiz03: {
                    question: "Which level of AI refers to machines that can perform any intellectual task that a human can?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Narrow AI",
                        option02: "Broad AI",
                        option03: "General AI",
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option03",
                    explanation: "General AI refers to machines that can perform any intellectual task that a human can. Unlike Narrow AI, which is limited to specific tasks, General AI has the ability to think abstractly, strategize, and use previous experiences to come up with new ideas."
                },
                quiz04: {
                    question: "Which of the following methods of learning describes how an AI system learns using trial and error?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Supervised learning",
                        option02: "Reinforcement learning",
                        option03: "Unsupervised learning",
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "Reinforcement learning is a machine learning model similar to supervised learning, but the algorithm isn’t trained using sample data. The model learns as it goes by using trial and error."
                },
                quiz05: {
                    question: "Reinforcement learning is a machine learning model similar to supervised learning, but the algorithm isn’t trained using sample data. The model learns as it goes by using trial and error.",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Structured",
                        option02: "Systematic",
                        option03: "Organized",
                        option04: "Unstructured "
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option04",
                    explanation: "Machine learning can analyze unstructured data more quickly than a programmable computer because machine learning doesn’t rely on programming instructions to work with unstructured data."
                },
                quiz06: {
                    question: "Which of the following is an example of structured data?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Videos",
                        option02: "Flight schedules",
                        option03: "Social media posts",
                        option04: "Movie reviews"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "Structured data is typically information that can be organized in rows and columns, such as flight schedules that include departure times, arrival times, and flight numbers."
                },
                quiz07: {
                    question: "Which of the following is a likely consequence of AI becoming more pervasive across industries?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Reliance on current machine interface technologies will strengthened",
                        option02: "Humans and machine interactions will become increasingly standardized",
                        option03: "Enhanced productivity and the creation of new opportunities",
                        option04: "Increased compartmentalization of AI implementation"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option03",
                    explanation: "AI everywhere suggests that as AI moves into all industries, from finance, to education, to healthcare it will promote productivity and enable new opportunities for everyone."
                },
                quiz08: {
                    question: "Which of the following explains why an AI trained with machine learning can rapidly map the best route between two points on a map?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "It relies on a complete database of all possible routes through the city.",
                        option02: "It predicts traffic problems based on stored alternative routes for every possible situation.",
                        option03: "It uses predefined programming instructions to navigate through traffic.",
                        option04: "It performs millions of tiny calculations quickly, trying different routes through trial and error. "
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option04",
                    explanation: "An AI trained with machine learning approaches the problem of finding the best route like climbing a tree, trying different routes and comparing successful ones to identify the shortest route. This process involves performing millions of tiny calculations quickly through trial and error."
                },
                quiz09: {
                    question: "You’re working for an employer who wants to learn from social media what customers say about her products and services. Which of the following is the best reason to support moving to an AI system?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Social media data is completely structured.",
                        option02: "Social media data contains a mix of structured and unstructured data.",
                        option03: "Social media data is completely unstructured.",
                        option04: "Social media data lacks complexity."
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "Social media data is semi-structured, meaning it has features of both structured and unstructured data. Semi-structured data doesn’t have a predefined data model."
                },

                quiz10: {
                    question: "Which of the following acts on behalf of people in the physical world in a way that complements human abilities?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Machine learning algorithms",
                        option02: "Augmented intelligence",
                        option03: "Cognitive computing systems",
                        option04: "Expert systems"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "Augmented intelligence systems enhance human abilities. Examples include screen readers for the blind, voice-driven navigation, and in-car collision avoidance systems."
                },

                quiz11: {
                    question: "Which of the following is the level of AI that is more versatile, can handle a wider range of related tasks, and is focused on integrating AI within specific business processes?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "General AI",
                        option02: "Broad AI",
                        option03: "Narrow AI",
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option02",
                    explanation: "Broad AI is a midpoint between Narrow AI and General AI and can handle a wider range of related tasks than Narrow AI, while focusing on integrating AI within specific business processes. Broad AI is not able to perform all of the intellectual tasks that humans can."
                },

                quiz12: {
                    question: "You are working on an AI system to help doctors treat patients. While describing your system to a group of doctors, you are asked the following question, 'How does machine learning enable decision-making in complex scenarios, such as medical treatment choices?' Which of the following is the best response?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "By providing probabilistic statements with confidence levels for different treatment options",
                        option02: "By ignoring potential outcomes and personal experience in decision making",
                        option03: "By offering deterministic solutions based on fixed criteria",
                        option04: "By relying solely on AI systems to make treatment decisions without human input"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option01",
                    explanation: "A machine learning system does not eliminate a doctor’s role in a treatment decision by suggesting 'Do this' or 'Do that'. Instead, machine learning systems provide probabilities of success for different treatment options allowing doctors and patients to make more informed decisions."
                },

                quiz13: {
                    question: "Which of the following types of data is categorized as qualitative data, and cannot be processed and analyzed by conventional data tools and methods?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Structured data",
                        option02: "Semi-structured data",
                        option03: "Unstructured data",
                        option04: "Data in a database"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option03",
                    explanation: "Unstructured data, sometimes referred to as dark data, lacks any built-in organization or structure."
                },

                quiz14: {
                    question: "Which of the following describes how machine learning differs from classical systems in structuring unstructured data?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Machine learning relies on deterministic algorithms to process unstructured data.",
                        option02: "Machine learning constructs a predetermined structure of routes based on a database.",
                        option03: "Machine learning offers probabilistic statements instead of binary decisions.",
                        option04: "Machine learning relies on human judgment to structure unstructured data."
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option03",
                    explanation: "Machine learning is probabilistic. It never says 'YES' or 'NO'. Machine learning is analog (like waves gradually going up and down) rather than binary (like a coin flip)."
                },

                quiz15: {
                    question: "Which of the following statements most accurately describes semi-structured data?",
                    options: {
                        option01: "Data that combines features of both structured and unstructured data, using metadata for organization",
                        option02: "Quantitative data processed and analyzed by conventional data tools",
                        option03: "Data that lacks any built-in organization or structure, such as images and texts",
                        option04: "Information that can be organized in rows and columns, like in a spreadsheet"
                    },
                    correctAnswer: "option01",
                    explanation: "Semi-structured data acts as a bridge between structured and unstructured data, incorporating elements of both while using metadata to identify specific characteristics and facilitate organization for improved cataloging, searching, and analysis."
                }


            }
        }
    }
}